Can you tell me the authority?
I don't do this medication by achieve a Miami fire department or proper proper.
Robert, thank you.
Father, I thank you for this day and I thank you for this group of people.
I thank you for the council, leadership, that they provided the community.
I thank you for the departments and each person and the work they do for this community.
I pray for the J.K. to say, watch over, Skydner, I just know that.
To be with the decisions, make days that we please and do you.
I thank you most of all for your time.
Jesus Christ, it's in his name up right.
In the ground, would you like to pledge?
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America.
To be the Republic for wish and say, one nation, I thank you for this opportunity to attend this ceremony.
Thank you, Ryan.
Thank you, Robert.
I am the fourth public input on Skydner Personal Baritains and you should address the authority on the United
States of America.
I don't know if I was considered to have the City of America at the set of seven, which
retains the grants.
Now, the question is on you and others, we have a motion to approve the consent to it as recommended.
I'll make a motion.
Second, roll call.
I'd like to ask.
Hi, Councillor.
Hi, or Cate?
OK.
I'd like to ask.
On this, I'd like to ask.
and a totally real patient to be reimbursed by the God.
Yes, sir, this is for Olsen to do the engineering
for the 698 project from the low water crossing there
by Puri, Puri, Casino, Buffalo, and Casino,
all the way to the railroad tracks, that portion right there.
So this is the electric in the water that's in this location.
O'Dow will be reimbursing us for everything.
We've already got a letter in the mail that they're
reimbursing us, they've already approved the work order.
We just have to formally approve it on our end.
Any questions on any of that?
Anything that you want?
No?
All right.
No, Motu approved?
Motion approved.
Yes, sir.
Second, roll, roll, please.
Western.
For Stern.
Lewis, I work it.
All right, so.
I don't know if I'm going to park on the environmental quality
for whom I have a permit to discharge.
On, Harry, I'm good, how are you?
Good.
OK, so this form,
here is to renew our discharge from the waste work.
Is there every five years we've got to do it?
R's is expires April 2020.
So if they want this information, I had it six months
that had it times so they can review it.
It's due to November 2nd.
I want to touch base on a piece of thing, because if you
park half of all the three of me with me on that form,
actually go to page 9, I wanted to tell you about these,
because I didn't want you to run it.
why they weren't building up. We no longer have any permanent interest. We're still a pre-treat
city, but we don't have any permanent interest. That's why this is a left blank. And I
will point that out in the cover that I said to the YouTube. And then also page 10, we don't reclaim
our water. So that page is left blank too. You might have seen in there really not numbers. A bunch
of spreadsheets with the box of those number. That is three years average weight of all the testing
within. They want that in an average of the last three years to see how the plants do. That's
how they based on what they're going to put in that permit for us to do. That was one of the
requirements that's in there. And then this big one at the very back, I don't know how it was
put in you guys' deal. But one of the things that asked for was a, that wanted to submit a
24-hour composite sample of all the pollutants in Table 2 and Table 3. Table 3 is, these are
pollutants that are identified by EPA and the categorized. Table 3 is metal cyanide and being all
if we run those twice a year. And in Table 2 is, there are a bunch of pollutants, it's like a hundred
or something. We do that once a year. So that's in there. All of this idea we do is, we'll go to DQ with
exception of couple of things. One is, it's fine here. In general public notice in there, get out of
it and I'll probably send a newspaper and then I'll be in half a day with Table 2. And then also we will
put in a copy of the invoice and they want to check for the feed on that for the yeah 15.
Then what I need from you guys is I'll pay six of that for and it's a third vacation, you know, the
design and no surprise. Okay? Right here. And on the test that we run on the one here in twice a year animals,
are we doing well on those and we're running away with them. The only thing that we've had a kind of high
hit on and think, I'm not sure why, that they haven't said anything to you. It's been high for years and years
and years and years. They might say, you know, one year they said, hey, we want you to run a copper for
one year starting in year three and a perfect. They might say that 15. I don't know, what they'll do
they'll review this and then they'll come down to the plant in inspection. But it'll get a different type of
inspection. It'll be one where they'll want to see if we change any of the treatment process without them knowing.
which we have. It's like a wet. So I can see what there would be zink on our stormwater run off,
but it's fluid, it's on the spread and that's without infiltration.
I don't know if you know some of that might come from some of the mind and stuff, a picture,
and if you don't want to run off, it's ended as frequent point.
And we'll create a lot of it in there.
And this doesn't have to be approved by anything.
It's not required to be approved by the board.
We don't have to take a vote on what you just need to sign.
We'd ask that you need to prove it, just make it formal approval tonight.
And you said we don't have any of the industries listed on that one chart any more.
So what did we have?
We used to have eight of the picture per minute.
Still cracked.
There you go.
Whenever they work and then blitz.
And the reason blitz was because they were making a metal gasket.
Now it's a flat back in the day.
So now they've gotten completely rid of that.
They don't need to do that.
But once you get three permanent industries in your city,
you become a pre-treative of a city.
DQ gives it to you and you take care of it.
But it doesn't matter if they're all gone.
They can be gone for 10 years.
They're not going to take it back.
You get to keep it.
Okay.
And Tyler, Tyler, what do you want us to do?
Just to prove this submission of the form?
Yes, they're in the application.
So you can sign off on that and we'll be good.
So do we have a motion to approve the application?
First submission.
I'll make a motion.
And the second.
Second.
Go call please.
Forster.
Orket.
Question.
Who is high school?
Thank you.
You business.
11 staff reports.
Question.
Staff's available.
12.
It's a trustee community announcement.
I'll send you an announcement.
But 10 is a German.
We have a motion to adjourn.
And I'll second that.
Call.
My 10.
Coach.